{
    "id": "a8a88fad574540288361961308570089",
    "title": "Finite and non-finite verbs",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "b57a3fe58127417d8db6d0347e540216",
            "title": "Finite And Non-finite Verbs Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "My little brother 'wants' to be an actor.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "finite",
                        "non-finite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She worked hard 'to pass' the test.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "finite",
                        "non-finite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I 'couldnâ€™t solve' the problem.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "finite",
                        "non-finite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "'To err' is human.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "finite",
                        "non-finite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Your duty is 'to cross' the river without getting noticed.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "finite",
                        "non-finite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The doctor 'is attending' to the injured people.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "finite",
                        "non-finite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She 'opened' the door.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "finite",
                        "non-finite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The students were asked 'to submit' their assignments by Friday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "finite",
                        "non-finite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The teacher 'encouraged' the students to work hard.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "finite",
                        "non-finite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The dog 'wagged' its tail to show its happiness.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "finite",
                        "non-finite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}